<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <string name="shortcutoff">Screen Off Run</string>
    <string name="shortcuton">Stop Screen Off</string>
    <string name="mannually_open">Please enable Accessibility service manually</string>
    <string name="active_first">Please start Screen Off Run service first</string>
    <string name="disagree">Disagree</string>
    <string name="agree">Agree</string>
    <string name="privacy">Privacy Policy</string>
    <string name="privacypolicy">This software does not collect, record, or upload any of your information.</string>
    <string name="toosmall">Too small!</string>
    <string name="all_ok">Service activated</string>
    <string name="not_ok">Tap to activate Screen Off Run</string>
    <string name="active_steps">Screen Off Run requires ADB or Root permission to activate.\nADB method: Enable USB Debugging on your phone, connect to a computer, and run the following command in a terminal/cmd window:\nadb shell %s\n\nFor devices with Android 6.0 and above, you can also use Shizuku to activate (Shizuku activation is essentially the same as ADB permission activation).\n</string>
    <string name="need_active">Screen Off Run service activation required</string>
    <string name="copy_cmd">Copy Command</string>
    <string name="cmd_copy_finish">ADB command copied to clipboard: adb shell %s</string>
    <string name="by_root">Activate via Root</string>
    <string name="active_failed">Activation failed</string>
    <string name="by_shizuku">Activate via Shizuku</string>
    <string name="key_pressed">You pressed the %s key\nKey code: %d</string>
    <string name="shizuku_notrun">Shizuku is not running</string>
    <string name="help_title">Help</string>
    <string name="help_conntent">You can tap the \"Screen Off Run\" title on the main interface at any time to open this help screen.\n\n\nWhile Screen Off Run is active, all apps will continue to work just as they do when the screen is on. You don\'t need to worry about the system automatically sleeping after a period of inactivity; as long as you enable the Global Control service and Floating Ball, the system will not sleep automatically unless you manually press the power button.\n\n\nWhen the \"Raise to Wake\" feature is enabled, the app monitors device orientation changes after the screen is off. This consumes a very small, almost negligible amount of battery.\n\n\nNote: Most devices block touch input when the screen is off via this method, so double-tap to wake only works on a few devices (such as Samsung S-Pen tablets, iQOO 9, Redmi Note 1 LTE, etc.).\n\n\nA few devices block hardware keys after the screen is off, so using volume keys to wake won\'t work on those devices (e.g., some Huawei HarmonyOS or Origin OS phones). Users with these devices can contact me to research using the getevent command to detect volume keys, which might be a viable workaround.\n\n\nSome LCD devices still have a backlight active after the screen is turned off this way. Similar to blocking keys or touch, this is determined by system engineers and cannot be changed by the app. However, you can minimize the backlight by lowering the screen brightness to the minimum before using Screen Off Run.</string>
    <string name="understand">Understood</string>
    <string name="start_global_control">Enable Global Control</string>
    <string name="show_fw">Show Floating Ball</string>
    <string name="show_only_land">Show only in landscape</string>
    <string name="lock_fw">Lock Floating Ball position</string>
    <string name="double_tap">Double tap to wake</string>
    <string name="orientation">Raise to wake</string>
    <string name="key_control">Key control screen state</string>
    <string name="scroff">Screen Off</string>
    <string name="scron">Screen On</string>
    <string name="fw_size">Floating Ball Size</string>
    <string name="fw_tran">Floating Ball Transparency</string>
    <string name="ori_sensity">Raise detection sensitivity</string>
    <string name="tile">Global Control</string>
    <string name="service_closed">Screen Off Run service closed</string>
    <string name="net_ctl">Network control screen state</string>
</resources>